<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist gettext-domain="gnome-shell-extensions">
    <schema path="/org/gnome/shell/extensions/netspeed/" id="org.gnome.shell.extensions.netspeed">
	<key name="interfaces" type="as">
            <default>["eno1", "wlp12s0b1", "enp13s0"]</default>
            <summary>Interfaces to monitor.</summary>
            <description>A list of interface names to track statistics on.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="update-interval" type="i">
            <default>1</default>
            <range min="1" max="60"/>
            <summary>Seconds between updates.</summary>
            <description>How often (in seconds) to update interface statistics.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="display-vertical" type="b">
            <default>false</default>
            <summary>Whether to display vertically.</summary>
            <description>When set to true statistics will be displayed one above another, rather than side by side. Requires that the panel is thick enough to accomodate multiple lines of text.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="decimal-place" type="i">
            <default>2</default>
            <range min="0" max="3" />
            <summary>Decimal places to use in measurements.</summary>
            <description>How many decimal places to use in measurements.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="custom-font-family" type="s">
            <default>"monospace"</default>
            <summary>Custom font family for display of statistics.</summary>
            <description>Generic CSS font family to display statistics in, instead of the default for your shell theme.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-font-size" type="i">
            <default>11</default>
            <range min="1" max="24" />
            <summary>Custom font size for display of statistics.</summary>
            <description>Font size in pt to display statistics in, instead of the default for your shell theme.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="use-fixed-width" type="b">
            <default>false</default>
            <summary>Whether statistics should be displayed with fixed width.</summary>
            <description>Whether statistics should be displayed with fixed width, as opposed to only taking as much room as the current value.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="width-is-minimum" type="b">
            <default>false</default>
            <summary>Whether the custom fixed width should be used as a minimum width.</summary>
            <description>Whether the custom fixed width should be used as a minimum width, still allowing the space alloted to expand if a longer value is displayed.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="custom-fixed-width" type="i">
            <default>48</default>
            <summary>Width to assign to each statistic.</summary>
            <description>Width to assign to each statistic. Statistics will be right-aligned within alloted space.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="use-custom-font-family" type="b">
            <default>false</default>
            <summary>Whether to use a custom font family.</summary>
            <description>Enables the custom font family for display of all statistics.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="use-custom-font-size" type="b">
            <default>false</default>
            <summary>Whether to use a custom font size.</summary>
            <description>Enables the custom font size for display of all statistics.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="use-custom-font-colours" type="b">
            <default>false</default>
            <summary>Whether to use custom font colours.</summary>
            <description>Enables custom font colours for display of each statistic.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="use-custom-decorations" type="b">
            <default>false</default>
            <summary>Whether to use custom statistic decorations.</summary>
            <description>Enables use of custom text at the end of each statistic.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="show-speed-down" type="b">
            <default>true</default>
            <summary>Whether to show current download speed.</summary>
            <description>Enables the display of the current net download speed across all monitored interfaces.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="show-speed-up" type="b">
            <default>true</default>
            <summary>Whether to show current upload speed.</summary>
            <description>Enables the display of the current net upload speed across all monitored interfaces.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="show-speed-total" type="b">
            <default>true</default>
            <summary>Whether to show current total speed.</summary>
            <description>Enables the display of the current total speed across all tracked interfaces.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="show-usage-total" type="b">
            <default>true</default>
            <summary>Whether to show total usage since last reboot or reset.</summary>
            <description>Enables the display of the total network usage on tracked interfaces since the last reboot, or the last usage reset, whichever was more recent.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-speed-down-colour" type="s">
            <default>"#FFFFFF"</default>
            <summary>Custom colour for the download speed statistic.</summary>
            <description>A custom colour to display the download speed statistic in, as a hex colour code.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-speed-up-colour" type="s">
            <default>"#FFFFFF"</default>
            <summary>Custom colour for the upload speed statistic.</summary>
            <description>A custom colour to display the upload speed statistic in, as a hex colour code.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-speed-total-colour" type="s">
            <default>"#FFFFFF"</default>
            <summary>Custom colour for the total speed statistic.</summary>
            <description>A custom colour to display the total speed statistic in, as a hex colour code.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-usage-total-colour" type="s">
            <default>"#FFFFFF"</default>
            <summary>Custom colour for total usage statistic.</summary>
            <description>A custom colour to display the total usage statistic in, as a hex colour code.</description>
	</key>
        <key name="custom-speed-down-decoration" type="s">
            <default>" D"</default>
            <summary>Custom text to decorate download speed statistic with.</summary>
            <description>A custom string which can be placed at the end of the download speed statistic.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-speed-up-decoration" type="s">
            <default>" U"</default>
            <summary>Custom text to decorate download speed statistic with.</summary>
            <description>A custom string which can be placed at the end of the upload speed statistic.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-speed-total-decoration" type="s">
            <default>" T"</default>
            <summary>Custom text to decorate download speed statistic with.</summary>
            <description>A custom string which can be placed at the end of the total speed statistic.</description>
        </key>
        <key name="custom-usage-total-decoration" type="s">
            <default>" U"</default>
            <summary>Custom text to decorate download speed statistic with.</summary>
            <description>A custom string which can be placed at the end of the total usage statistic.</description>
	</key>

	<key name="initial-receive-count" type="d">
            <default>0</default>
            <summary>Total initial received bytes saved from last session.</summary>
            <description>Total received bytes from when the extension was last enabled. Used to persist usage records across shell restarts.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="initial-transmit-count" type="d">
            <default>0</default>
            <summary>Total initial transmitted bytes saved from last session.</summary>
            <description>Total transmitted bytes from when the extension was last enabled. Used to persist usage records across shell restarts.</description>
        </key>
	<key name="last-boot-time" type="d">
            <default>0</default>
            <summary>Boot time as of last time the extension was run.</summary>
            <description>Boot time of the system when the extension was last disabled. Used to check of previous initial recieve/transmit counts should be used.</description>
        </key>
    </schema>
</schemalist>

